<Document>
# Apid
<Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobApid" Caption=""/>
</Box>
Apids, or "Beefolk" as they are sometimes colloquially known, are a unique asset to Nanotrasen's logistics network.

They are a eusocial species, forming "hives" with a high degree of organization and efficiency. Under a recent contract, Apids have easily integrated into the Nanotrasen work structure, providing reliable, well trained labour on short term notice.

## Physiology
Apids possess uniquely weak limbs, rendering them incapable of maneuvering normally on the ground - however, [color=#1e90ff]their strong wings and ultralight physiology enable them to fly continuously under standard NT gravity[/color], and allows them to [color=#1e90ff]easily outpace most other Nanotrasen-dealing species while doing so.[/color]

This reliance on being airborne does come with significant disadvantages - [color=#ffa500]Their weak forelimbs are only capable of holding aloft one object at a time,[/color] meaning for all intents and purposes they only have one hand. As well as this, [color=#ffa500]the placement of their wings prevents them from wearing backpacks, jetpacks, or suit tanks[/color].

In addition, their lightweight build leaves [color=#ffa500]significantly more vulnerable to physical trauma, going critical at only 60 damage[/color], and they have a [color=#ffa500]tendency to become drowsy when exposed to atmospheric water vapor[/color].

  ## Apid Naming Conventions
  Apids originate from a utilitarian society, and as of such, their naming traditions are similarly utilitarian. Their "first name" is generally a simple title of the work they enjoy, with their "last name" being a mononym in their native language.
  - [color=#449944]Acceptable:[/color] Baker R'zvsszsr
  - [color=#449944]Acceptable:[/color] Playwright S'rzvz
  - [color=#449944]Acceptable:[/color] Builder S'vszs-vs
  - [color=#449944]Acceptable:[/color] Technician Zs'vsz
  - [color=#994444]Bad:[/color] Motherfucker Unlimited
  - [color=#994444]Bad:[/color] Barry B. Benson
  - [color=#994444]Bad:[/color] Not the Bees
  - [color=#994444]Bad:[/color] Benry

</Document>
